I did your horoscope, remember?
I was gonna do everybody's until Sheldon
went on one of his psychotic rants.
(Sheldon:)For the record, that psychotic rant...
(Sheldon:)...was a concise summation
of the research of Bertram Forer...
(Sheldon:)...who, in 1948, proved conclusively...
...through meticulous experiments...
(Sheldon:)...that astrology
is pseudoscientific hokum.
Blah, blah, blah. Typical Taurus.
- So we gonna see you Saturday?
- I don't think so.
(Penny:)- Why not?
- I don't celebrate my birthday.
Shut up. Yeah, you do.
(Leonard:)It's no big deal.
It's the way I was raised.
My parents focused
on celebrating achievements...
(Leonard:)...and being expelled from a birth canal
was not considered one of them.
(Penny:)- That's so silly.
- It's actually based on very sound theories.
(Sheldon:)- His mother published a paper on it.
- Well, what was it called?
"I Hate My Son
and That's Why He Can't Have Cake"?
SHELDON:
It was obviously effective.
(Sheldon:)Leonard grew up to be
an experimental physicist.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps if she'd also denied him Christmas,
he'd be a little better at it.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Howard:)Well, I love birthdays. Waking up
to Mom's special French-toast breakfast...